{
    "id": "d6ecb5683d4b410e8e0a35c20829f77e",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "As Tom was suffering from fever, he ...................... go to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't",
                "couldn't",
                "won't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ecac330383a4f8ba831fc87b26d854b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He speaks as if he knows the truth. (Perhaps he does.)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knows",
                "knew",
                "has known"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4da2a57527a4889b3754f9052dfeb9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rekha was clever enough to see ...................... the scam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "through",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e0bdd8eb6bf94ee1a3d2eb1c04a0f3d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .................... old to walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f91a4e232403495a8863d025d120bf71"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ....................... angry that she said nothing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f86177f22c2544e8942472e7c9f6023a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you not ashamed ....................... your conduct?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6133ecebbd694553adc5df394270144a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The older you get, .......................... you become.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wise",
                "wiser",
                "wisest",
                "the wiser"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "04e4e95bb3694d109efb84bb428a6ce0"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had I opened the book, ...................... I started feeling sleepy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "336a4c0631fa463ca355aafb60fa2bad"
        },
        {
            "question": "The room was .................... small to accommodate the guests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b7b9e48f328d43e5bd1041f0e2db0996"
        },
        {
            "question": "The night was ....................... dark that I couldnâ€™t see anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c09a99dc3e44e0682bb37ef6dbf9ad3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Booker was ......................... timid to speak up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "197b7f5410ec41f7b57b5f478f328b00"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................... being ill, she went to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Though",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b4f95bff1eb84292a23f784f34f60e4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I .................. taller.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "678636992e7b4872b56c6414a69f9808"
        }
    ]
}